One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
The Invisible Man and
the Secret of the Mansion!
We're traveling pira-
I mean, sailors!
We were traveling and lost our way!
Please let us in!
Is anyone home?
That's weird, the inside looks like a tunnel.
I can see a courtyard on the other side.
Sorry to intrude!
You think he's out?
That wouldn't be good.
If we go back, the zombies'll get us.
Look, a light just went on!
Actually, it's more of a spotlight.
It's shining on this well...
Welcome.
One, two, three.
W-What?
Four, five.
O-Ow!
She's attacking us with plates!
Six, seven.
Ow, are you only aiming at me?!
Yes, that's right.
You aren't allowed in the mansion.
You two over there can come in.
Eh? Why?
You aren't going anywhere!
Eight, nine!
Why?
Stop, that's enough!
What?
No more scary stuff, please!
Someone else is there?
Can't you make just one exception, Cindry-chan?
I'm sorry for scaring you like that.
Long ago, in order to test the love of her rich fiancé,
This woman broke all of his expensive china plates,
and was chased off and led a horrible life.
My plate-hating servant, Cindry-chan.
Okay... whatever.
And I still haven't introduced myself...
Master of the Mansion (Genius Surgeon)
Doctor Hogback
I am the world-renowned Doctor Hogback!
And I'm a genius.
Ten!
Usopp!
W-Wait, Cindry-chan!
I told you to stop that!
You're supposed to listen to what I have to say!
I wish plates would disappear from this world.
I understand!
I really do understand, but right now I'm trying to talk!
Chopper...
That's the guy you wanted to...
D-Doctor Hogback, it's really him!
He looks kinda idiotic.
Stop it, Nami!
Well, we can continue this inside.
We can make an exception and allow all three of you in.
So, welcome.
T-That's right, come in.
I don't understand why I couldn't go in...
But anyway, let's go.
Yeah, it's at least better than the zombies.
Hey, I'm still...!
I'm... still here...
I'd like to welcome you to my mansion!
You guys are so dirty!
Why are you here?
Well, a lot of reasons...
Firstly...
I wanna talk to you later!
We were attacked by zombies in the graveyard, and we ran here!
Zombies?
We've seen loads of other unbelievable creatures here too!
What's up with this place?
You live here, you should know!
Oh, you were attacked?
I'm glad you made it here safely.
That's great.
As for your question, here's my answer:
I live here because I don't know what those things are.
So, you're here to research the zombies, Doctor?!
Of course!
Humans have a horrible fear of zombies.
But if we look at it as people coming back from the dead instead...
Then isn't it the immortality all humans strive for?
Everyone has one or two deceased people close to them that they wish to see again...
With medical science, we are capable of controlling whether people live or die, fearless of the gods!
It was for that reason I went exile to begin my research on this mysterious island.
R-Really?
But if you succeed, there'll be tons of people that'll be happy!
I'll cheer you on, Doctor Hogback!
Oh, thank you, Doctor Chopper.
E-Even if you call me a doctor, I'm not happy, asshole!
Can I have your autograph?
Oh, sure.
To Doctor Chopper-kun,
And later, can I see your lab?
Don't you ever even look at my lab...!
Oh, Cindry-chan, can't you at least put the pudding on a plate?
Or is it hopeless to ask?!
I wish for all plates to be gone.
Well, don't worry, we keep the tablecloth clean just for occasions like this!
Then, let's eat!
You could at least use a spoon!
Oh! It's really sweet and good!
I have prepared the bath.
You're all dirty, so you can use it.
Oh yeah, old man!
This is all fine, but...
You didn't happen to see a weird skeleton pass by, did you?
A-A skeleton?
Yeah.
He's got an afro, he's real tall...
He's really light...
Well, I guess it's weird enough being a walking, talking skeleton.
Do you know anything about it?
No, I don't.
Really?
Oh well.
Do they mean that guy?
No... it can't be...
Mansion's Bath
I don't really have any interest in seeing human women naked...
But I do wanna sneak a peek at Doctor Hogback's lab.
But really, Nami,
why do we have to keep watch for you like this?
If you're that scared, you could've skipped the bath!
You know, for being grabbed by zombies like that, you two sure don't seem to care.
You're filthy!
We're just gonna get dirty again!
Yeah!
Tonight, we're leaving.
What are you, stupi-
They told us we could spend the night.
Do you know what could happen to us if we went out tonight?!
Anyway, we're not gonna go anywhere else.
Luffy and the others are gonna come and save us.
Okay?
I agree!
I don't wanna go back out there!
I don't like that forest, nor the graves!
The inside is the same as the outside.
Have you taken a good look around?
If I'm not mistaken,
The halls and rooms are full.
This mansion is filled with zombies.
W-Where are they?!
But the most suspicious of all is Hogback himself.
He's definitely lying.
If he really didn't have any connection to the zombies like he says,
why would he be living in a mansion filled with them?
W-What about you, Chopper?
If that's really true, then...
No...
So for now, we'll just pretend we don't know,
And we'll leave tonight.
Well, well, what a tricky girl.
What?
Usopp, Chopper, did one of you say something?
I didn't say anything.
Hey, I just farted!
Ew, gross, Usopp!
I'm Usopoo!
You damn...!
What's happening?
There's nobody here...!
Compared to that woman on the ship...
You're a lot weaker - more my type.
There's someone here...!
Usopp, Cho-
You... are going to be my bride.
Hey Nami, what happened?
Can you smell Usopp's fart in here too?
Thank you very much!
You're thanking her?
Get out...
Stupid, help me...!
Damn you...!
Usopp, Chopper, help!
There's someone here!
She's right, I can smell it!
Still?
Sorry!
Not the fart, a person!
He's going out the window!
How is the window doing that on its own?
What's getting away?
Deadly Gunpowder Star!
I wonder if he got away...
He heard our whole conversation...
H-Hey, Nami, what just happened?
I don't get it!
He was here the whole time...
An invisible man.
It's no good.
Meanwhile... in the Thousand Sunny
Luffy and the Others
No matter what we do, we can't get out.
From this huge spiderweb...
That skeleton's ship is stuck too, just like the Sunny.
And the Mini Merry Usopp and the others were riding is stuck here too.
With the front gate like that, it's almost like it's calling to you.
Damn.
I can almost see all the little ghosts beckoning us in.
What're you going on about over there, Zoro?
You need to come too!
If you stay here you'll just be bored.
Let's go!
You can even share some of my bento!
Why are there stairs all of a sudden?
It's 'cause this is the entrance!
Hey, it's full of skeletons.
Oh, Cerberus?
Hell would probably be safer than this place.
Oh, it's cute.
You think it can fight?
Dunno.
You think it tastes good?
It wants a fight now.
So I'll just...
No, hold on.
I'm gonna try taming it.
Idiot, I know it's a dog, but come on.
It looks more like a boss or something.
Dog like dog.
There there...
Paw!
Right after we warned him...
There there, good boy...
There there...
That's it, let go nice and easy...
That's a good boy...
Bastard!
Down.
That's just wrong.
But ignoring that, it has horrible scarring on it.
It simply remaining alive is a mystery in itself.
It looks like a fox got mixed into it, so I doubt it's really a normal animal.
Man, fun things are just showing up as soon as we get here, it's great!
Cerberus-san doesn't seem too happy.
Having it do something like this after losing is really damaging its pride.
Nami-san!
Hey!
Where are you, Nami-swan!?
Nami-san!
We left the tunnel, and now we're in a forest?
This is weird.
Huh?
An old man tree...
and a unicorn...
are drinking together...!
Help!
Gotcha!
Please let me go!
Hey you guys, come be pirates with-
Stop that!
Doctor Hogback's Mansion
That was a close one...
Hey, Absalom.
I know you're here.
What was that commotion just now?
Were you in the bathing room again?
I was looking for a bride.
I like that woman.
I'll make her mine.
Well, you're not getting any of the bounty money.
What's that?
This time, six of them have bounties.
One of them is over 100 million,
and the captain himself is 300 million!
300 million?
Are you sure, Perona?
The government doesn't put a bounty like that on an ordinary pirate.
And now that we know that, we'll put all of our power into capturing them, Absalom.
Tonight we have our work cut out for us!
There's no such thing as an invisible man!
Inside the Mansion
Second Floor Hallway
There was one!
Didn't you see him attacking me?!
Uh, well...
No, I didn't!
Yes you did!
You're tricking me!
You just want me to tell you I saw you naked so you can charge me!
I was gonna die!
Although I'm still gonna charge you.
Anyway, I don't believe anything we've seen on this island!
Listen!
The invisible man? Your imagination.
The ghosts? Weird birds.
The zombies are a race of...
mysterious underground dwellers!
What are you talking about?
It's true we saw a skeleton brought back to life with a devil fruit.
But!
That was just an exception to the rule!
No two people can have the same devil fruit ability,
And there's no other way people can be brought back to life!
Right, Chopper?
There's no other way something like that can happen!
Even with medicine, there isn't any way something like that should be possible.
But...
Doctor Hogback is really amazing, and he's researching it.
It's possible even something as miraculous as that is going on here!
Don't you trust him a little too much?
Doctor Hogback is a great man!
I respect him a lot!
You're the one in the wrong!
You're saying the doctor and the zombies are together without any proof!
I can't shake off the feeling we're being watched...
It's weird.
Oh well...
That's the room from before, right?
Yeah...
Why is it so dark?
What?
C-Cindry-chan?
Doctor!
Where'd you go?
Thank you for the bath...
The two of them have retired for the night.
Hildon?!
Why you...
You just left us out in that graveyard earlier!
I had no choice.
I took the horses to go do something, and when I wasn't looking...
You're lying!
All of you on this island are ghouls!
T-That's insulting.
Now if you'll follow me, I'll show you your rooms...
You're just ignoring all that, and showing us around?!
I wonder if that's really the door to hell?
We're just gonna leave now, sorry.
Please let me talk to the doctor again first!
They found us out, Hildon...
Please ignore that, and I'll show you your rooms...
It's alright.
They've already started to figure it all out...
So before they get away...
Why is...
that painting...
talk- talk- talk-
You're cute when you're shaking in fear!
Chopper!
A zombie came out of the picture?!
Save me!
Chopper!
The leader of the zombies in this room is I, Buhichuck-sama!
Don't think you'll be able to take even one step out of this room, oink!
T-That mounted head just talked?
Ow, ow, ow...
Who just stabbed that sword in my back?
It's just like Nami said!
This mansion really is filled with zombies!
Usopp!
Why you...
Take this, you stupid rug-bear!
No, it's a candle!
Hot, hot!
Get it away, I'll burn!
It's fire, I'm scared!
Put it out!
He's on the chandelier!
Knock him down, fast!
I know your weakness!
Take this, all of you!
Take that!
and that!
Chopper, Nami, get to the door!
We're getting out of here!
Okay!
Let's get out!
I've had enough!
Hurry and get it open!
There're lots of them here too!
What are you doing, Nami?!
No...!
D-Don't tell me...
It won't open!
We're trapped!
You've really done it now.
You won't get away from us!
Damn pirates!
Get down!
That was close!
Anyway, let's get out of here!
We'll go to a different room!
We won't let you get away!
No, no, no!
Stop!
We're in the fireplace!
There's nowhere else to run!
Where are we?
Hey, they disappeared!
They disappeared into the fireplace!
Crap, they opened the secret passage!
They'll be in Hogback-sama's laboratory!
Follow them!
It's no good, it's blocked from the other side!
No matter where they go in this mansion, the other Surprise Zombies are there, oink!
We need to get out of this tunnel, and stay out of rooms with paintings!
Where's a room?
Over there!
More paintings!
No, photos?
Good...
They aren't zombies.
Isn't this... that girl?
The plate-hating one, Cindry-chan?
What is this place?
Now that I look at her again, she's really pretty...
That servant Cindry-chan...
So... is this her room?
Come on, would you really put this many pictures of yourself in your own room?
But she had stitches all over her face and body!
Yeah... these pictures don't show any at all.
It can't really be a different person...
Maybe they're really old?
Victoria Cindry.
It looks like she was a really famous actress.
Look, all of these articles are about her.
An actress?
Didn't they say something earlier about her not being a servant?
Something about breaking plates and being thrown out by her husband...
Looking at this, I just don't think something like that happened.
She was born into a rich family...
She was very popular ever since she was a child...
What is it?
Ten years ago...
She fell from the stage...
and died!
W-W-What the hell are you talking about?!
She's alive, isn't she?!
She's not dead, right?!
But if that report really is true,
that means she already died once and came back to life!
On this island... those were all real zombies...
What we saw... really were living dead!
No way...
This is just getting even creepier!
I wish I hadn't known tha-
What?!
Wait, Usopp!
Isn't that a treasure chest~?
That was a fast change!
Hey, Usopp, open it!
Please open it up for me?
Sorry, this isn't where we keep the treasure!
Jack-in-the-box!
Stay out!
Painting zombies!
"This isn't where we keep the treasure."
That's what that jack-in-the-box zombie said.
Oh, it's the guard.
It seems as if there are people lost in this mansion.
Oh, it's you?
That isn't a problem...
I will subdue them.
You need to stop trying to make everything your friend!
Our crew already has weird shit like a raccoon dog and a robot!
Hey, I'm not a robot!
I'm a cyborg, bastard!
What matters is that you aren't human!
But my base was human!
No, your base was a pervert!
Oh, well, if you say it that way...
It wasn't a compliment...
I wonder what we'll find next?
This is so much fun!
About that tree person and that unicorn...
What is it?
All of the strange animals we've seen in this forest have similar characteristics...
Bandages.
Stitches.
And a number tattooed onto them.
A number...
I guess it does have one.
So you mean someone's doing this to them?
Yes, most likely.
Hm? What's that sound?
There, it's a ghost!
They're all dancing and wiggling!
Cool!
They sound kinda freaky.
I'll catch one for a pet!
So they can phase through things...
Alright!
Fresh Fire!
No, that didn't work either.
I'm worthless.
This week's me is just completely worthless.
No matter what I do, I fail.
I don't have the will to live...
I can hear the whole world booing at me...
Why are you getting so depressed?!
Alright!
Bastard!
If I were to be reborn,
I want to be a shellfish.
I'm the worst ever...
I wish there was a hole I could be buried in...
Really, what the hell are you guys doing?!
Perhaps if you're touched by the ghosts, then you have feelings of worthlessness?
That doesn't make sense!
They're pathetic.
They never try their hardest anyway,
So these ghosts are able to play games with their hearts.
I'm sorry I was ever born...
Enough of that!
It seems it's just like Robin-chan said.
Even without physical body, they're still able to cause such emotional distress with a simple touch.
If they are our enemies, they're very strong.
Definitely.
This really is a mysterious island.
Oh, next time I see those ghosts, I'm not holding back!
And I won't get one as a pet, I don't want it!
They've gotta have a weakness!
This time, I'll get rid of 'em!
Damn, that was just too funny!
Shut up!
The patchwork animals with numbers may very well be created...
But those ghosts seem to be something entirely different.
Those guys were on the boat too.
I get the feeling they're showing up every once in a while just to spy on us...
So the question is, who's behind all of this?
Wow, what a huge graveyard!
This place is really cool!
Hey, let's eat our bento here!
Idiot, if you eat it here, the food will taste nasty!
There, there, there...
Why the hell would I wanna go back?!
Is it a badly injured old guy?
It's a zombie, obviously!
Underestimating us zombies...
is something you shouldn't do!
Are zombies really this lively?
We'll show you how dangerous zombies really are!
Oh, you wanna fight?
Then we'll show you just how dangerous we are.
600 Million Belly Jackpot!
What are you guys doing here?
Um, zombie stuff... being buried.
Rotting...
Yeah, rotting.
Yeah, me too.
Are you messing with me?
No, no! We're not! We're sorry!
Have a man with a long nose...
a woman with orange hair...
and a reindeer-like raccoon dog passed through here?
Ah, yes, yes, yes...
But we won't tell you!
We have orders not to give anyone information like that.
Orders! Orders! Orders! Orders!
Oh? So you absolutely won't tell us?
Those three came through.
They're my friends.
You didn't touch them, right?
Eh...?!
T-They were your friends?
I-I didn't!
Neither did I!
Tell me the truth!
He touched them!
Eh?! Don't sell out a friend!
You're the one that tried to bite them!
We all attacked together.
Idiot! Don't say that!
It looks like they headed towards that mansion.
Glad they're okay.
Though we still don't know about Brook...
But that's alright, isn't it?
W-Wait a minute!
I saw you just now.
You're terribly strong, right?
Would you listen to my story for a moment?
You're badly wounded. What happened?!
We told you, he's a zombie!
No, I'm a badly wounded old man.
You're too easy to confuse! We'll just call you a zombie!
There's a man I want you to beat.
I know you guys can do it!
There are so many victims... if he was defeated they would all be saved.
I would be so grateful if I got my shadow back.
It's true! You're missing your shadow too, old man?
Just like Brook!
Who did this?
Is it someone on this island?
Moriah...
A man known as Moriah.
He's really frightening!
Moriah?
Could you be referring to...
Gekko Moriah?
That's it, that Moriah!
Robin, you know him?
I know his name very well.
He's a man whose former bounty exceeds even yours, Luffy...!
Gekko Moriah is...
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!